Where's Lilliel-chan? Is everything okay?
Ririsa...!
Lilliel...
First Event Is Over!!
Ashford-sama!
Sorry that took so long.
Lilliel...
You're here.
Where's that cutie been all this time?!
Who is that?
She's gotta be famous!
I don't know her.
How'd we miss her?
This event isn't that big!
Did she just get changed?
There's only ten minutes left!
T-that's True Angel Lilliel!
She said Lilliel and I shrugged
it off for being so old...
but look at me now!
What is this flutter in my heart,
as if I've just been reunited with my first crush?!
Every man goes through a Lilliel phase.
I did, too, back when I wouldn't
even call myself an otaku.
Here she is, the Lilliel I loved so dearly back then!
And in such a high-quality costume!
I can never let milady Magino
know these treacherous feelings!
Wait, Lilliel?
That was that girl?!
Cancel what I said about heading out.
I'm right there with you, bro.
How do you want to get photos taken?
I've never done this before...
Maybe if you start taking pictures,
everyone else will start, too?
We need to find a spot, first...
Can I take your picture?
Do you have a card?!
What's your handle?
Are you selling cosroms?!
Um, uh...
Ogino, don't you want to get pictures of her?
Surely you're not serious!
I wouldn't dare betray you, milady!
Are you crying blood?!
SHOUT SHOUT
ARGUE ARGUE
Lilliel! Lilliel!
I want you to get good pictures of her!
C'mon, go!
Are you doing photos now? Thanks!
Sure!
Wait, is there a line?
There's not enough time to go through a whole line!
Huh?!
You guys need to ask her what she wants.
L-Lilliel...
This is getting crazy.
And we're almost out of time.
She needs a handler.
Attention, everyone!
Miss Lilliel here is ready for photos!
It's her first time, so let's all be extra polite!
Her first time?!
May we use this space here?
Sure!
Thank you, miss!
I have the honor of organizing
this last-minute photoshoot!
To expedite things,
please gather around in a semi-circle!
T-thank you so much!
Please.
This means I'm allowed to have the best spot!
So he does want pictures...
Thank you!
Y-yes, thank you!
Stop bowing!
You're not some disgraced CEO, Lilliel!
I-I gotta strike a pose!
I can't squeeze in...
Yeah, not with this huge crowd.
Look over here, please!
Huh?
Over here!
Wait, I don't know where to look!
Careful!
Ririsa!
S-sorry about that!
Phew...
She's a newbie, all right.
She doesn't have her posing down yet, either.
Wish she'd hit some classic poses.
It's like she doesn't know what we want.
I dunno, her inexperience makes her so much cuter!
T-these simpletons!
Do they know nothing about the source material?!
All her poses are straight from the manga and anime!
And she's not just doing poses from the key art,
but one-off pages and panels, too!
She changes it every five seconds...
She must be doing this by heart!
She's clearly a diehard Lilliel fan!
What do you think, Ogino?
W-well, she's clearly not as incredible as you, milady!
But, I must admit...
It is a display worthy of the utmost respect!
Yeah, she's cute.
What's your opinion,
as a self-proclaimed cosplay reviewer?
It was hard to get good photos of her
because she's not used
to posing for a semicircle.
Yeah...
But...
It doesn't feel like she's wearing a costume.
Haven't heard that from you before.
What does that mean?
Not sure how else to put it.
It just doesn't feel like cosplay.
Maybe because she feels
the opposite of professional,
it instead feels more raw?
It's like this is just how she always is.
Like the real Lilliel stepped out from
the pages and posed for my camera.
Bro...
Wouldn't that make her perfect?
I wonder how I look to them.
Can they tell how much I love Lilliel?
Because I love her...
...so, so much!
Get as many pics as you can before
it's midnight and the spell wears off.
One more minute, everyone!
What?!
Ririsa?!
What is my daughter doing
with these filthy comics?
I'm sorry, Mom. But they're not-
Tell me this is some kind of mistake!
Huh?!
A mistake...
This is the first time
I've gone out in public as Lilliel!
Ten seconds!
Nine! Eight! Seven!
Over here!
A real otaku NEVER judges
someone by the things they love!
Your Lilliel is the cutest in the entire world!
Senpai did this.
Senpai gave me the courage to do this.
Three! Two! One!
Thank you!
That last expression was so cute.
Definitely the cutest of the bunch.
That's the loving gaze she gives
her darling Lord Ashford!
Wish she would've looked my way...
Sorry, Lilliel.
Senpai!
I missed my chance to get good pictures.
Can I take one now?
Of course!
I'm feeling so relieved, I'm smiling all funny.
Here we go.
Wait, Senpai!
Huh?!
I was way too relaxed there!
I wasn't in character as Lilliel!
Can we take another?
I dunno.
This one came out great, Ririsa.
See you later!
Yeah, see ya!
Spring CosFest 19 is now officially over.
The changing rooms will close at 5 PM.
Women's
Changing Room
Lilliel-san!
Y-yes?
Wait, -san?
I want your cosrom!
Can I buy it online?!
S-sorry, I don't have that set up...
Can I post your photos online?
Sorry, please don't post them!
Could I at least get your card?
You gotta have a social media handle!
Lilliel-chan, the changing room's gonna close soon!
Sorry, I don't have either...
I'll be right there!
Sorry, I have to change!
No cards, no socials...
Who the hell was she?
A shapeshifter?
An angel, idiot.
Yay!
The changing room is closing soon!
Okay!
Lilliel-chan, mind if I get one with you?
S-sure!
Really?
It looks like Lilliel's gotten way
too into some skeevy host.
Nah, more like an angel's come
to take Akito off to heaven.
Do I look dead?!
We're closing the room soon!
Women's Changing Room
Crap, gotta hurry!
I had so much fun today!
Lilliel-chan, got a second?
Sure.
Could you take my tail off?
The glue just won't budge.
It's not sewn into your costume!
You actually have it on your tailbone!
Well, yeah, I want it to look perfect.
Magino-chan, you still dealing with allergies?
I assume that's why you've got so many masks.
Oh, no.
Those are for my safety.
I've done a lot of animal-themed cosplay lately.
So they're for fur and dust.
Sometimes, I wonder if my lungs will give
out from the amount of fur I've inhaled.
X-RAY
But I can't stop cosplaying those characters.
Yeah, I get it.
I always say I want to try a bunch of different genres,
but then I look in my closet and
it's just full of kimonos.
I know that feel.
Bakiko, you're always doing
characters with horns or fangs.
Yup.
I was heading home from an event once
and noticed a bunch of people staring at me...
...'cause I'd forgotten to take my fangs out.
Yikes.
You gotta be more careful.
Says the girl still wearing her elf ears!
Well, since we're all telling horror stories...
Wait, these are horror stories?
One time, I was lounging around after an event...
...when I heard my brother screaming
bloody murder in the bathroom.
I'd left my wig soaking in the tub...
Yeah, that's a horror story, all right!
That happened to me, too.
My wig was drying and fell
down on top of the TV.
Total Sadako moment.
Hey, what're you guys all chatting about?
W-who're you?!
Oh, c'mon. It's me, Akito.
Oh, sorry...
She's handsome even out of her cosplay...
I've got a scary story to share.
Like I said, this wasn't supposed to be all scary stories...
You've heard of cosplayers'
partners finding their wigs
and thinking they're cheating, right?
In my case,
my family's always finding mens' jackets
and stuff hanging around my room.
They know I cosplay,
but they don't know
I'm usually doing male characters.
Not like they ask me all that much about it, anyway.
So one day my mom tells me...
Mom
I wish you'd at least break up with the
guy who wears those leather jackets...
What?
Apparently, they thought I was dating
seven different guys at once.
I bet you don't have any cosplay
worries just yet, Lilliel-chan.
Huh?!
Your skin is perfect, you're super adorable,
and you've got a great figure to boot.
Stop flirting!
Y-you're wrong, I've got plenty of worries.
I'm really short, but I have big boobs,
and my proportions always
make things harder for me.
Like, I can never find good clothes in my size!
Yeah, I get that.
I want to do all sorts of cosplays,
but anything that isn't skin
tight just makes me look fat!
So I'm probably cursed...
Cursed to only look good in skimpy outfits!
SKIN TIGHT!
Outfits I'm too embarrassed to wear!
MIDRIFF EXPOSED,
T&A ON DISPLAY
There, there.
Your outfit was really cute today, though.
I cheated. I had a professional help me pick this out.
professional
What?
I cheated. I had a professional help me pick this out.
Did you, now?
What the heck does that mean?
What do you usually wear?
Got any pics?
Here's the one I showed her.
See? None of them fit right!
The fit's not the problem.
It's your fashion sense.
The happy peace sign makes it so much sadder.
Not that I'm gonna tell her that...
COSPLAYER STORYTIME: END
Where's the elf lady?
I have her undies!
I gotta give her her undies!
You mean her ruffle shorts?
Don't go shouting 'undies,' girl.
She just left.
What?! I had no idea...
It's okay.
It's hard to tell who's who out of costume.
She said you could keep it.
Yeah, but... Let me go try to find her!
I've got to get going,
but thank you all so much for all your help!
Lilliel-chan!
Yeah?
Hope we'll see you at Summer Comiket!
Summer Comiket...
I can't believe she didn't have any socials or a card.
I hope we see her again.
Summer Comiket!
RIRISA AMANO
They kicked us out so I’m waiting at the station.
OK, I’ll be there in a sec!
Senpai!
Ririsa!
Sorry that took so long!
You sure you're good?
There's another train in 40 minutes.
No, just, uh...
Elf lady! Elf lady, are you still here?
Elf lady!
Excuse me, you're looking for an elf lady?
Yes, she had long ears...
Actually, probably not anymore!
Long ears?
She's an elf lady.
Has anyone seen an elf lady?
Elf! Elf lady!
What the hell is happening?
Has anyone seen an elf lady?
Elf lady!
Can you be quiet?! You're embarrassing me!
Hi, I'm the 'elf lady.'
She's so pretty!
Is this your partner?
Y-yes, ma'am!
E-elf lady, I-
I work at an office nearby, so zip those lips!
No one would guess she's an otaku...
Um, here!
I wanted to make sure I returned them!
You could've kept them, you know...
How'd your first cosrom fare?
W-well, we made a bunch of mistakes,
and ended up not selling a single one.
Yikes...
Your first one's always a bomb, though.
Mayura sold zero copies for her first, too.
Really?!
She's inspired me to make an incredible cosrom,
just like hers!
Great.
Oh, right! Where was she today?
So...
Mayura probably isn't going to cosplay events anymore.
Huh?! Is she quitting cosplay for good?!
Kind of.
She's trying to wash her hands of it, I guess.
What, like cosplay's a criminal record?
Things are just tougher when
you're older and have a job.
I'll tell her you say hi, though.
Ririsa, is Mayura that one cosplayer?
Yes, she did Milky Succubus.
That doesn't sound good then... Right?
We didn't sell any DVDs,
and her inspiration just up and quit...
H-how do I make her feel better?
Don't worry about me, Senpai.
If I keep going to events,
I'm sure I'll run into her again someday!
And I want to see all my new friends again, too!
Senpai! I want to go to Summer Comiket!
Summer Comiket?
Things didn't work out today,
but I want to keep making even better cosroms,
and keep going to more events!
Good. Guess I didn't need to worry.
I mean, she's been holding
onto this dream for quite a while.
W-will you help me?
Yeah, of course. Why're you even asking?
The only reason I got to make a cosrom
and go to an event is because you helped me.
That's not true. You put in a ton of effort.
No, it's true!
I could only do it because you were there helping me!
Without you, I...
Ririsa?
I've... I've noticed I feel a little
weird around you lately, Senpai.
My heart starts to beat fast,
and when you kept me safe that one time,
my chest felt really tight.
Wait, what?
Come to think of it,
when I'm alone with her, I feel weird...
So it's not just me?! Does that mean we're...
I wasn't sure what it was before,
but today I finally figured out what I'm feeling.
And I think it's important that I tell you, too.
Senpai, this feeling is love.
Wait, like...
Because I love having you as my cosplay partner!
It all made sense after the event today!
I'm so happy I've found a
photographer as amazing as you!
Oh...
Oh, okay!
She loves having me as a partner!
Yep, that makes total sense!
So I wasn't feeling anything romantic towards her, either!
I was jealous because I'm her photographer, that's all!
My heart races around him 'cause
I've got so much respect for him as a cosplayer!
Here I was getting worried I'd fallen in love with him!
Then I'd be the one making
our relationship complicated!
Aww, c'mon.
Thank god!
THEY’RE BOTH IDIOTS.
Senpai's Secret Special Training!?